<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference on gogolok</title>
    <link>https://gogolok.github.io/tags/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conference on gogolok</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 23:42:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://gogolok.github.io/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Railswaycon 2012 Mobile Backends in Ruby on Rails</title>
      <link>https://gogolok.github.io/posts/railswaycon-2012-mobile-backends-in-ruby-on-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 23:42:59 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gogolok.github.io/posts/railswaycon-2012-mobile-backends-in-ruby-on-rails/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Julian Fischer Avarteq GmbH und Robert Gogolok Avarteq GmbH&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;17.10.2012 | 10:30 – 11:30 Uhr | Zagrebsaal 2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ruby on Rails has become a well accepted and highly appreciated tool for building modern web apps. A complete and well cultivated eco system has been created over the years. Now the increasing demand for mobile applications raises a demand for well designed (JSON) APIs to talk to. It is not less than a perfect match. Ruby on Rails is so sweet to build both web apps as well as APIs to be consumed by mobile apps. In this talk you will have a look at common challenges such as authentication, designing the API’s JSON structures as well as how to minimize traffic between your mobile app and its backend. Exemplary ways to encounter those challenges will be illustrated on both sides: the rails server and the mobile app. At the end of this talk you will have a basic plan on how to approach a mobile app using Ruby on Rails and how build its backend, easily.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euruko 2012 Trip Report</title>
      <link>https://gogolok.github.io/posts/euruko-2012-trip-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 23:07:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gogolok.github.io/posts/euruko-2012-trip-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, I was able to attend Euruko 2012 in Amsterdam with a few of my colleagues from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.avarteq.de/&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Avarteq&lt;/a&gt;. We arrived thursday night, hence we missed the boat party at thursday night.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The conference was held in the Pathé Tuschinski. Pathé Tuschinski is a beautiful movie theatre. Nearly 600 attendees occupied the theatre, quite amazing, as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hone02/status/208491286217490434/photo/1/large&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;“Happy Friday Hug”&lt;/a&gt; depicts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My favorite talk at the conference was “JRuby, dudes!” by Charles Nutter. He successfully gave an in-depth presentation of JRuby with practical examples. I also liked the beginner friendly talk “Ruby’s big men” by Elise Huard. Elise &lt;a href=&#34;https://speakerdeck.com/u/elise_huard/p/rubys-bin-men&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;described in a simple manner&lt;/a&gt;  the garbage collector in Ruby and its various implementations. As an iOS developer I also enjoyed Eloy Duran with his talk about &lt;a href=&#34;http://cocoapods.org/&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CocoaPods&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
